

Contact

Phone +91 97061 86907

Email priyanujdey@live.com

Address Goregaon East Mumbai - 63

Website https://priyanuj.com

Education

2017 - 2020 B. Sc in Filmmaking - VFX Whistling Woods International

2015 - 2017 Sr. Secondary Kokrajhar Govt. College

Priyanuj Dey

Video Editor & Visual Effects Artist

🗑 priynju in priyanujdey 🚺 priyanujdey

Profile

Experienced Video Editor & Visual Effects Artist adept in meeting client needs throughout the entirety of the process. Able to handle multiple projects simultaneously while providing the highest level of service, quality, and creativity. Accustomed to working well with others and committed to meeting deadlines and adhering to project guidelines.

Experience

Jan 2021 - May 2022 Associate Video Editor

QAD Inc

Jan 2021 - May 2022 Sr Video Editor & Motion Graphics Artist

Fitpage

Handlied all in-house video production
which included videos for Mobile app,

Youtube and Social media.

2017 - Present Visual Effects & GFX Artist

Freelance Artist

Adept in tracking & matchmove, chroma

keying, 3D Object placement, FX and various forms of Motion Graphics.

2018 - Present VFX Artist

Karkhana Studio Responsible for handling all in-house visual

effects requirement of the studio.

Skills

Premier Pro Houdini Houdini

Nuke After Effects Tracking